本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
恭喜了  Charlie  今天是个很特别的日子
Well, Charlie, today is a very special day.
今天是你的一周岁生日
It's your first birthday!
一家子都激动得要为你庆祝呢
The whole family's excited to celebrate.
生日快乐  甜心
Happy Birthday, sweetie.
我爱你哦  小宝贝
I love you, baby girl.
你是最棒的哟
You're the best.
我就是来等着吃蛋糕的
I'm just here for the cake.
好吧  Duncan一家五人中有四个比较激动
Well, four out of the five Duncans are excited.
好啦  谁想送给Charlie她人生的第一份生日礼物
Okay, who wants to give Charlie her first present?
哦  我来  我来
Oh, I do, I do!
看来PJ想要第一个表现哦
I think p.J. Wants to go first.
你还记得你以前说过她需要有件睡衣吗
Okay, you know how you said she needed something to sleep in?
看这个
Well...
看到没  PJ版的睡衣呀
Get it? P.J.'s pjs.
-很酷吧  老爸  - 呃  是不错
- Pretty cool, huh, dad?- Yeah, they're great.
你能喜欢真是太好了  因为其实那家店是有二合一套餐的
I'm glad you like them--because there was a two-for-one deal...
提前恭祝你今年生日快乐了 老爸
Happy early birthday, dad.
小伙子  这礼物还真难转送出去
Boy, those are gonna be tough to regift.
到你了  Gabe
Your turn, Gabe.
就在桌上那个棕色袋子里头
It's in the brown bag on the table.
喔唷  你的包装还真不错啊
Oooh, nice presentation.
《死吧  僵尸  去死》
"Die, Zombies, Die"?
咋啦  打僵尸要从娃娃抓起
Hey, you're never too young to learn how to kill zombies.
好啦  下一个还是瞧我的
Okay, I'm next.
好吧  让我们来瞧瞧这里头有啥
All right, let's see what we have here.
好漂亮呀
So pretty.
哦  宝贝
Oh, baby.
Teddy  这可真贴心
Teddy, that is so sweet.
是吧  至少这不是《死吧  僵尸  去死》
Well, it's no "Die, Zombies, Die."
哎呀  这不是Charlie出生那天我们拍的照片吗
Hey, that's the picture we took the day Charlie was born.
那天可真够乱套的  不是吗
What a crazy day, huh?
一开始一点也不乱套啊
It didn't start out that way.
我还记得是多么兴奋地带着你这小快活球到处跑呢
I remember how excited I was to be carrying my little bundle of joy.
噢哟  我真等不及要把这玩意儿弄出去了
Oh, I can't wait to get this thing out of here!
你听见了没  快出去
You heard her-- get out.
她说的是肚子里的婴儿啦  对吗  妈妈
She's talking about the baby. Right, mom?
哇塞  这是啥怪味儿
Whoa, what is that smell?
我怀孕了  我会胀气  你该习惯了
I'm pregnant. I have gas. Deal with it.
不  不是那个  比那还糟呢
No, not that. It's worse.
确实如此  其实这怪味就来自于你的午餐
No, actually that smell is coming from your lunch.
老爸又为你们今天的钓鱼旅行做了他的经典鸡蛋沙拉
Dad made his famous egg salad for your fishing trip today.
鸡蛋莎拉  晕  连鱼都不想吃那玩意儿
Egg salad? Even the fish hate the smell of that.
而且那味道还跟鱼是一样的呢
And they smell like fish.
嘿  P.J  你准备好出去找点乐子了吗
Hey, p.J., you ready to go have some fun?
我是想啊  可我这不是得跟你去钓鱼吗
Yeah, but I have to go fishing with you.
哦  老爸  你能捎我去学校吗
Oh, hey, dad, can you drop me off at school?
Ivy和我今天想去搞我们那个儿童剧场的事儿
Ivy and I are doing our children's theater thing today
- 我们要穿演戏的服装呢  - 当然可以
- And we need to get into costumes. - Sure.
哦  Gabe啊  要是你没事做也可以来看我们表演哦
Oh, and, Gabe, if you're not doing anything you can come see it.
我自己写的哦  知道不  是一则很有趣的寓言故事
I wrote it, you know? It's a delightful fable
故事说的是啊  一群来自不同世界的人们
About people from different worlds
克服了他们彼此的差异从而成为了朋友
Who overcome their differences and become friends.
哇
Wow...
听你一说  我倒觉得去钓鱼反而有趣起来了
You actually made the fishing trip sound fun.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
Today's all burnt toast
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
Running late, and dad jokes
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
Has anybody seen my left shoe
■
翻译： Colonel C
我闭上双眼  咬口早餐
I close my eyes, take a bite
跳上车子  放声大笑
Grab a ride, laugh out loud
发现鞋子被扔在了屋顶上
There it is up on the roof
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
I've been there, I've survived
所以听取我的建议
So just take my advice
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, baby,
■
校订  后期： WaitinZ
世界有很多疯狂无奈
Things are crazy
可是我知道你会有美好未来
But I know your future is bright
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
不要怀疑
There is no maybe
一切终会如你所愿
Eveything turns out all right
生活有悲有喜
Sure life is up and down
可是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
But trust me, it comes back all around
你会喜欢将来的你
You're gonna love who you turn out to be
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
查莉成长日记  第一季第八集
Good Luck Charlie  S01E08  Charlie is 1
再来一点好了
A little more.
为了好运气再加最后一点
And one for good luck.
噢哟  噢哟
Oh oh!
不会吧  你至少也让我吃完这盘威化饼干啊
Really? Can't you at least wait until I finish my waffle?
好吧  我们照您的指示来
Okay, we'll do it your way.
Bob亲爱的  时候到了  宝宝要生出来了
Bob, honey, it's time. The baby's coming.
啥 你预产期不是在三个星期之后嘛
<i>What?! You're not due for another three weeks.</i>
我正在湖当中啊
<i>I'm in the middle of the lake.</i>
你能不能先冷静下来
Would you please just calm down?
我都已经生过三个了  第四个当然也没问题
I've done this three times already. I can do it a fourth.
还有啊  我要给你说清楚  绝对不要第五个了
And just so we're clear, there will not be a fifth.
PJ  我们得赶快去医院
<i>PJ, we've got to get to the hospital.</i>
- 哦别别别  你不能站在独木舟上  - 为什么不行啊
<i>- No no no, you can't stand up in the canoe. - Why not?</i>
因为啊
Becau--
你好  我是Amy Duncan
Hi, um, this is Amy Duncan.
我想找Singh医生
I'm calling for Dr. Singh.
是的  请您转告他  我现在有分娩阵痛了
Yes, could you please let him know that I have gone into labor?
希望和他在医院会面
And to meet me at the hospital?
好的  非常感谢  再见
Okay, thank you very much. Bye-bye.
好吧  看来我们要赤着脚去了
Okay, we're gonna do this barefoot.
咱们去生孩子吧
Let's go have a baby.
妈妈
Mom!
喂
Hello?
有人在家吗
Is anyone home?
嘿嘿  那就没人告诉我不能做这种事啦
Then no one can tell me not to do this.
嗯
Mmm!
好吃啊
Mmm.
行啦  就算是我弄翻了小船
Okay, I tipped over the boat.
你还要我说几次对不起啊
How many times can I say I'm sorry?
我们要开四十五英里路去医院  有的是时间让你道歉
We've got a 45-mile drive to the hospital, I guess we'll find out.
- 那是一头熊吗  -跑到卡车里去了  它是怎么钻进去的啊
- Is that a bear? - In the truck? How'd he get in there?
我可不知道  儿子  你自己去问它好了
I don't know, son. Why don't you ask him?
- 我们怎么把它弄出来呢 - 还是别惹它的好
<i>- How do we get him out? - We don't.</i>
它是熊老大  它说了算
He's the bear. He makes the decisions.
老爸  你是灭害专家耶  你应该能搞定的
Dad, you're an exterminator. You should deal with this.
我是可以  只要它再瘦六百磅  并且能合上一个捕鼠器的尺寸
I will-- when he loses 600 lbs and fits in a mousetrap.
那我们现在怎么去医院啊
How are we gonna get to the hospital?
走着去  来吧  我们赶紧走
Start walking. Come on, let's go.
不是吧  它把所有的鸡蛋沙拉三明治都吃光了
Oh, man! He ate all the egg salad sandwiches.
哦  猛啊  我爱熊老大
Oh, yes! I love that bear.
哟  很好嘛  今年提早过万圣节啊
Oh, good, Halloween's come early this year.
你是要扮的谁啊
Who are you two supposed to be?
我是弗兰肯斯坦  她是格雷特
I'm Frankenstein and she's Gretel.
我们是要表演我自己写的剧本来着
It's for a play I wrote.
我看不懂
I don't get it.
观众们也没看懂
Neither did the audience.
你胡说什么呢  才不是呢  孩子们可喜欢了
What are you talking about? No, the kids loved it.
你那扁脑袋是脑壳坏掉了吧
Are you out of your flat head?
表演就是一场灾难啊
It was a disaster.
那他们干嘛要鼓掌啊
Then why were they cheering?
那是欢送我们提早离场呢
Because we had to leave early.
我们是来找Amy Duncan的
We're here to see Amy Duncan.
就在那里面呢
Right in there.
当汉塞(格雷塔的弟弟)和德库拉(吸血鬼)来的时候
When Hansel and Dracula get here
我会放他们进去的
I'll send them in.
- 好啊  妈妈  - 好啊  科学怪人
- Hey, mom.  - Hi, Frankenstein.
好啊
Hi--
我看到这顶假发时也是一样的反应啊
I had the same reaction when I saw this wig.
是一阵痉挛
Contraction.
- 你还好吗  - 棒极了
- Are you okay? - Super, great.
好得不能再好了  我的小鸭子们都排成一行了
Couldn't be better. All my ducks are in a row
所有事都有条不紊
And everything's under control.
那Gabe在哪儿呢
So where's Gabe?
我看我是丢下了一只小鸭子在家里啊
I guess I left one of my ducks at home.
什么  Gabe独自呆在家啊
Wait, Gabe's home alone?
这可不是好事儿
Oh, that is not good.
Gabe  你没事吗
Gabe, you okay?
我觉得好极了
I'm awesome!
嘿  快看哪
Hey, check it out.
喂 喂  有人吗
Hey hey, anybody here?
老爸  你要做什么
Dad, what are you doing?
PJ  我们必须赶快去医院
P.J. , we've got to get to the hospital.
我来看看能不能把这些玩意用电线发动
I'm just gonna see if I can hotwire one of these things.
哎呀  老爸
Uh, dad!
你想偷我们的摩托车么
You trying to steal our bikes?
不是要偷  是用线发动
Not steal-- hotwire.
别  听我说啊  凡事三思啊  你们可能会后悔的
No, look look look, before you do something you might regret,
我真的有一个好理由的
There is a perfectly good explanation.
我倒想听听看
And I'd love to hear it...
就在我把你抽筋扒皮之后
Right after I gut you like a fish.
你要用你的大砍刀还是要巨砍刀
You want your big knife or your really big knife?
随便拿一个
Surprise me.
哟  Charlie真的很爱她的生日蛋糕呢
Boy, Charlie's really loving her birthday cake.
我就说啊  是不是老可爱了
I know. Isn't it adorable?
她这样就是可爱  我这样做就是不对
When she does it it's adorable. When I do it it's wrong.
那是因为当时我们是在饭店里  而且你吃的是别人的蛋糕
And that's because we were at a restaurant and it wasn't your cake.
行了  我们还是继续说之前的故事啊
Come on, let's get back to the story.
那些摩托车手们有没有把你抽筋扒皮啊
Did the bikers gut you like a fish?
- 你不是也在场的么  - 哦  对
- You were there.  - Oh, right.
好吧  说回来  车手们很强大
All right, anyway, bikers were coming on strong,
我就必须显示更强大
I had to come back stronger.
请别伤害我们  别伤害我们
Please don't hurt us. Please don't hurt us.
你倒是给我找个好理由啊
Give us one good reason why we shouldn't.
因为那会很疼的啊
Because it would hurt.
听着听着听着  你们不明白
Look look look, you don't understand.
我老婆要生了  而我们那卡车里有头熊
My wife is having a baby and there's a bear in our truck.
所以我才想借俩摩托
That's why I'm trying to borrow the bike.
我可不能错过自己孩子的出生啊
I can't-- I can't miss the birth of my child.
好感人啊
That's beautiful.
我们得帮帮这些人赶到医院去
We gotta help these people get to the hospital.
自从他开始刺绣后就好久没这样感性了
He hasn't been the same since he took up needlepoint.
哦  谢谢  太感谢你们这样帮忙了
Oh, thank you. Thank you so much for helping us out.
说到这个  我叫Bob  这是我儿子PJ
By the way, I'm Bob. This is my son P.J.
我们是疯狗和Francis
We're mad dog and Francis.
很高兴认识你  疯狗
Good to meet you, mad dog.
我是Francis  她才是疯狗
I'm Francis. She's mad dog.
我的真名叫雪莉  但如果你敢那么叫的话
My real name's Shirley. If you call me that...
你就会把我们抽筋扒皮吗
You'll gut him like a fish?
你小子挺识相的
You catch on real fast.
D太太  你能不能小点声啊
Mrs. D., can you keep it down a little bit?
我在抢演唱会的票呢
I'm trying to win concert tickets.
他在哪儿啊  我要开始害怕了
Where is he? I'm starting to get worried.
好了  妈妈  别紧张  我相信爸爸很快就到了
Okay, mom, relax. I'm sure dad's going to be here soon.
你爸  谁管你爸啊
Dad?! Who cares about dad?
我是说Singh医生
I'm talking about Dr. Singh.
他接生了我所有的孩子
He's delivered all my children.
小姐  没有他在  我才不要生这个宝宝呢
And, lady, I am not having this baby without him.
科学怪物  咱俩能不能去谈一谈
Frankenstein, can I talk to you a minute?
好的
Yep.
- Singh医生不在这儿  - 还没来吗
- Dr. Singh's not here. - Not yet?
不会来了 他请了私假  今天是他儿子的生日
Not at all. He's taking a personal day. It's his son's birthday.
你的意思是他根本不会来吗
So you mean he's not gonna be here.
听着  我知道你那脑子里还住着别人
Look, I know you have someone else's brain inside your head,
（科学怪物的分裂思维故事）
那让我来慢慢地给你讲清楚吧
So I'm gonna tell it to you slowly.
Singh  不  来  了
Singh not coming.
- 没什么事吧  - 一切都正常
- Is everything okay? - Everything's great.
就是有一点小问题
Just one tiny glitch.
- Singh医生不来啦  - 啊
- Dr. Singh's not coming. - Oh.
好吧  也行
All right, fine.
- 那你觉得无所谓吗  - 当然了
- So you're okay with this? - Of course.
说真的  妈妈  那可太好了  因为我还担心
Serious, mom, that's awesome, because I thought--
- 妈妈你干什么呢  - 回家啊
- What are you doing?  - Going home.
等明天Singh医生来了  我们再来生孩子
We'll just do this tomorrow when Dr. Singh can be here.
我觉得事情没你想的那么美  D太太
I don't think that's how it works, Mrs. D.
得了吧  宝宝在我肚子里呆了九个月了
Oh, come on, the baby's been in here nine months,
它可以再等等的
It can wait another day.
Ivy亲爱的  做个甜姐儿把我的脚塞到鞋子里吧
Ivy honey, be a dear and jam that shoe onto my foot.
呃  妈妈  请你回到床上去
Um, mom, please get back in bed.
没有Singh医生  我就不生
I am not gonna have this baby without Dr. Singh.
好的好的  那我们去把他找来就是
Okay okay, then we'll go get him.
- 你真的要去吗  - 我们会去的
- You will? - We will.
哦  那可真贴心
Oh, that's so nice.
好了  我们快跑吧  格雷特
All right, let's roll, Gretel.
这下好了  又要有更多人看到我这副样子了
Oh good, more people get to see me.
哦耶
Yeehaw!
新纪录啊
New record!
Gabe  我是Dabney太太  快开门
<i>Gabe, it's Mrs. Dabney. Open up.</i>
我不应该给陌生人开门
I'm not supposed to open the door to strangers.
我倒是指望我们互不认识呢  快让我进去
I wish we were strangers. Let me in.
这儿发生了什么事啊
<i>What is going on in here?</i>
是我一生中最美好的日子
Just the best day of my life.
派对结束  你姐姐打电话来  叫我领你去医院
Party's over. Your sister called and asked me to bring you to the hospital.
不要
No way.
我才不要大老远去就为瞧个呆宝宝
I'm not going just to see some stupid baby
我根本想都不想要它出生呢
Who I don't even want anyway.
我算是明白了  给我坐下
I see what's going on. Have a seat.
我来给你讲个故事
I'm gonna tell you a story.
我四岁的时候  小妹妹出生了
When I was four, I got a baby sister.
刚看她第一眼  我就恨那姑娘
Hated that girl from the first minute I laid eyes on her.
我拉过她的头发
I used to pull her hair
不停的叫她名字把她整哭
And call her names and tease her till she cried.
我们就这么长大了  恶性循环下来
But we grew up and one thing led to another
过了这么多年后  我还是和她处不来
And after all these years I still can't stand her.
你这样说怎么可能让我觉得好过
How is that supposed to make me feel better?
我又没说要让你觉得好过
I didn't say it was going to make you feel better.
我只说要给你讲个故事
I said I was going to tell you a story.
现在把那头盔脱下来  开路走
Now take that helmet off and let's go.
你的脑袋是怎么回事
What did you do to your head?
我自己剃了个头呀
Gave myself a haircut.
你喜欢这发型吗
You like it?
我希望有证据证明那是我来之前就发生的
I want it documented that that happened before I got here.
别别别别  不要  喂 喂
Wait wait wait wait, no, hey hey.
好了  时间到
All right, time out.
Singh医生
Dr. Singh?
哎呀  来的真及时  我正
Oh, it's about time. I--
等一下  我预订的是蝙蝠侠
Wait a minute. I ordered Batman.
不是科学怪人和  金发森林女吗
Not Frankenstein and... Goldilocks?
猜得挺接近了
Close enough.
不是的  我们不是为你的派对来的  你给我接生过的呀
No, we're not here for the party. You delivered me.
我要是接生过科学怪物  那绝对忘不了
I think I would have remembered that.
我是Teddy呀  Amy Duncan的女儿  她现在正要生孩子
I'm Teddy, Amy Duncan's daughter. She's about to give birth
- 需要您赶紧去医院  - 我走不开
- And needs you at the hospital. - I can't leave.
我得留在这儿享受我儿子的生日呢
I have to stay here and enjoy my son's birthday.
谁扔的  是不是你啊  Tyler
Who threw that? Was it you, Tyler?
还是另外一个Tyler呢
Or the other Tyler?
不不不不不
No no no no no.
别别别
No no no.
我们来做个交易吧  怎么样
How about we make a deal, okay?
若您能去医院照看我妈妈
If you go to the hospital and take care of my mom,
那我们就留下来娱乐这些孩子们
Then we'll stay here and entertain the kids.
我们怎么可能做得到
And how are we gonna do that?
给他们表演我的小话剧啊
We'll do my play for them.
这是一个有趣的寓言故事  说的是从不同世界来的人们
Oh, it's a delightful fable about people from different worlds
克服了彼此的差异  最终成为了朋友
Who overcome their differences and become friends.
给你两个拇指  祝你们好运
I give it two thumbs up. Good luck.
嘿  孩子们  有谁想看小话剧啊
Hey, kids, who wants to see a play, huh?
呃  看来Tyler投了赞成票
That is a yes from Tyler.
听着
Hey!
要是格雷塔被球打中了
If Gretel gets hit with a football,
这个派对上就要少一个Tyler了
There's gonna be one less Tyler at this party.
有好戏看了
This should be good.
我们刚才骑摩托跟着一辆大卡车上飞驰四十迈过来的
We just drove 40 miles behind a truck
那车上装满了活鸡
Loaded with live chickens on motorcycles.
鸡不是在摩托车上  摩托是我们骑的
The chickens weren't on motorcycles. We were.
- 你们一定是Duncan家的  - 你怎么会知道
- You must be the Duncans. - How'd you know that?
瞎猜的  进去吧
Wild guess. In there.
哦  多谢载我们过来  我们自己进去就可以了
Oh, uh, thanks for dropping us off. We can handle it from here.
哦  我们还不能走  我俩对这事儿也投入了好多感情呢
Oh, we can't leave now. We're emotionally invested.
再说我还想快速地冲个澡
And I need to grab a quick shower.
她是说真的
She's not kidding.
我真不敢相信你竟然敢在我车上吐
I can't believe you threw up in my car.
那你还指望什么
What did you expect?
午饭我就吃了两大罐子糖霜
For lunch I ate two cans of frosting.
我们找Amy Duncan
We're looking for Amy Duncan.
我们认识Duncan家的人
We know the Duncans.
交给你们了
Good enough for me.
- 我喜欢你的发型  - 谢谢哈
- I like your hair. - Thanks.
我喜欢你那伤疤
I like your scar.
您好  请问这个姜饼小屋里有人在吗
Hello, is anyone home in this gingerbread house?
科学怪人
Frankenstein?
你在德国和瑞士人的地方做什么啊
What are you doing in German Switzerland?
我想要朋友
Me want friend.
但是像你这样的大怪物
But how can a big monster like you
怎么可能和我这样甜美的小农家姑娘做朋友呢
Be friends with a sweet little peasant girl like me?
可以的哟  如果你们相信
It's possible. If you believe
我俩能成为朋友  就拍拍手吧
We can be friends, clap hands.
来拍拍手
Clap hands!
像这样
Like this!
T  放弃吧
T, give it up.
你在干什么  快照剧本念
What are you doing? Stick to the script.
看看他们吧  又蠢又无聊  我们还是别干了
Look at them. They're bored silly. Let's just stop.
不能停  科学怪还没得到爱的鼓励让他感动得哭呢
No, we can't. Frankenstein hasn't found the courage to cry yet.
不好意思  小弗弗  格雷塔现在要做主了
Sorry, Frankie, Gretel's taking over.
看哪  孩子们  谁想来玩往科学怪身上钉尾巴的游戏啊
Hey, kids, who wants to play pin the tail on the Frankenstein?
我要  我要  我要
Me me me!
这是我们儿子猪仔的照片
That's a picture of our son Hog.
他的名字叫猪仔
His name's Hog?
本来是的  但他现在改成叫凯文了
It was. He changed it to Kevin.
那小子真让人失望
The boy's been a real disappointment.
- 他是犯了罪还是怎么着  -比那更糟
- Is he like a criminal or something? - Worse.
他成了营销副总裁
Vice president of marketing.
- 第一个孩子吗  - 很明显看的出来  是吧
- First baby? - That obvious, huh?
嘿  我也经历过的
Hey, I've been there.
- 你吗  - 哦  对呀
- You have? - Oh yeah.
- 这都是我第三次坐在这儿等啦  - 哇
- This is my third time sitting in these chairs. - Wow.
要是不冒昧问句
If you don't mind my asking,
- 你第一次的时候几岁啊  - 两岁
- How old were you the first time? - Two.
- 妈妈生了没  - 还没
- Has mom given birth yet? - Nope.
- 喂  Teddy姐  - 你那头发是怎么回事
- Hey, Teddy. - What happened to your hair?
我正在用柔顺调理啊
I'm conditioning.
你就是Teddy
You're Teddy?
和Gabe小弟形容的一模一样
You're exactly like Gabe described you.
嘿  孩子们  都过来  想让你们见个人
Hey, kids, come on. There's somebody I want you to meet.
嗨
Hi.
进来吧  都进来
Come in, come in.
大家都来跟你们新诞生的小妹妹问好吧
Say hello to your new baby sister, everybody.
她的名字是Charlotte  你想抱抱她吗  Teddy
Her name is Charlotte. Do you want to hold her, Teddy?
- 我可以吗  - 当然了
- Can I? - Of course.
她真漂亮
She's beautiful.
你好啊
Hi there.
很高兴认识你哦
Nice to meet you.
还有我平常不是这幅模样的
And I don't usually look like this.
真不敢相信我有了一个小妹妹
I can't believe I have a baby sister.
请您给我们照张全家福好吗
Would you mind taking a picture?
谢谢
Thank you.
- 宝宝名叫什么啊  - Charlotte
- What's the baby's name? - Charlotte.
- 妈妈  我们可以叫她Charlie吗  - Charlie啊
- Mama, can we call her Charlie? - Charlie!
我喜欢这名字
Oh, I love it.
瞧瞧你们这一家子哟
Quite a family you got there.
祝你好运吧  Charlie
Good luck, Charlie.
甜心  我很喜欢这个礼物
Sweetie, I just love this present.
谢谢你  妈妈
Oh, thanks, mom.
不过公平的说  是因为PJ和Gabe把标准大大降低了
But to be fair, P.J. And Gabe set the bar pretty low.
- 乱讲  - 行了
- What?! - Hey.
惊喜吧
Surprise.
哦  疯狗  Francis
Oh, mad dog, Francis,
快请进
Come on in.
你们怎么会来啦
What are you guys doing here?
给我们的教女带礼物来啊
We have a birthday present for our goddaughter.
骑士婴儿装
A baby biker vest.
咱们给她穿上试试
Let's try it on.
真可爱  我好喜欢呀
That's so cute. I love it.
你让他们给宝宝做教父母了
Did you ask them to be the godparents?
当然没有了
Of course not.
那你得去跟他们说  他们不是教父教母
Then you have to tell them that they are not the godparents.
不用了  谢谢
No thank you.
好吧  那我去
Fine, I'll do it.
打扰下  我有事想跟你们说
Excuse me. There's something I have to tell you.
哎呀  欢迎加入我们一家
Oh, welcome to the family.
大家  快看哪
Guys, check it out.
- 噢哟  - 小可爱
- Ohhh! - Cutie.
我觉得我一定听到了什么声音
I know I heard something.
我想是从厨房传来的
I think it's coming from the kitchen.
好吧  你等在这儿
Okay, you wait here.
或者躲回楼上去
Or I could hide upstairs.
你是来找鸡蛋沙拉的吧
You're here for the egg salad, aren't you?
好吧  坐下好了
Okay, sit down.
你把我的卡车开回来了吗
You bring back my truck?
是不是加满了油的
Full tank of gas?
这都不懂  你是山顶洞人吗
What, were you raised in a cave?